<custom-action actionType="SapClick" isHit="true"
    name="Click GuiButton (Yes)" uid="63faca2e-4428-4377-8b9b-d878238b264b">
    <description>This action simulates a click action on an SAP GUI object.

Possible parameters are:&#xd;
- objectId (optional): The SAP GUI object identifier. Default value is "ses[0]/".&#xd;
- menuItem (optional): The id of the menu item.&#xd;
- toolbarButton (optional): The id of the toolbar button.&#xd;
- toolbarContextButton (optional): The id of the toolbar context button.&#xd;
- contextButton (optional): The id of the context button.&#xd;
- contextMenuItem (optional): The context menu item to select in a toolbar.&#xd;
- contextMenuItemText (optional): The context menu item text to select in a toolbar.&#xd;
- contextMenuItemPosition (optional): The context menu item position to select in a toolbar.&#xd;
- column (optional): The column index of a table or the column name of a grid.&#xd;
- row (optional): The row index of a grid or a table.&#xd;
- nodeKey (optional): The node key of a tree.&#xd;
- indexes (optional): The indexes separated by "/" to reference a tree path. Example: 0/1/1/2.&#xd;
- itemName (optional): The item name of a tree.&#xd;
- buttonPress (optional): If set to "true", a press button will be performed on a tree. Default value is "false".&#xd;
- clickLink (optional): If set to "true", a click link will be performed on a tree. Default value is "false".&#xd;
- changeCheckbox (optional): The value to set in a checkbox of a tree.&#xd;
- x (optional): The x coordinate when clicking on a picture.&#xd;
- y (optional): The y coordinate when clicking on a picture.&#xd;
- ignoreErrors (optional): If set to "true", the action won't be in error if object is not found, type is not supported or an exception is thrown. Default value is "false".&#xd;
- windowId (optional): The SAP GUI window identifier.&#xd;
- objectName (optional): The SAP GUI object name.&#xd;
- objectType (optional): The SAP GUI object type.</description>
    <custom-action-parameter name="objectId" type="TEXT" value="ses[0]/wnd[1]/usr/btnSPOP-OPTION1"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="objectName" type="TEXT" value="SPOP-OPTION1"/>
    <custom-action-parameter name="objectType" type="TEXT" value="GuiButton"/>
    <responsePageFileDescription>team/vus/@s@a@p_@user_@g/%resources%/recorded-responses/res_aa341379-d636-43c0-9128-a67f741974d6</responsePageFileDescription>
    <screenshotFileDescription>team/vus/@s@a@p_@user_@g/%resources%/recorded-screenshots/sc_aa341379-d636-43c0-9128-a67f741974d6.jpg</screenshotFileDescription>
</custom-action>
